Guide to the Duke Family papers on the Duke Farms residence, 1859-2004 and undated RL.01437
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Architectural Records, 1897-1992 and undated
  - Duke Farms Coach Barn, 1900-1901, 1939 and undated
    - Side Elevation, 4 of 11. Russel Associates. 1990 Mar. Pellet Print (Positive blueprint). (Oversize-folder C1D2F8)
    - Building Plan, 5 of 11. Russel Associates. 1990 Mar. Pellet Print (Positive blueprint). (Oversize-folder C1D2F8)
    - Cross Section, Longitudinal Section, and Section Looking at Stalls, 6 of 11. Russel Associates. 1990 Mar. Pellet Print (Positive blueprint). (Oversize-folder C1D2F8)
    - Pre-Engineered Steel Structure by Ceco Buildings Division, 7 of 11. Russel Associates. 1990 May. Pellet Print (Positive blueprint). (Oversize-folder C1D2F8)
    - Main Structure and Wall Section, 8 of 11. Russel Associates. 1990 May. Pellet Print (Positive blueprint). (Oversize-folder C1D2F8)
    - Plan of Stall, Grill Detail, Stall Elevation, and Side Section of Stall, 9 of 11. Russel Associates. [1990]. Pellet Print (Positive blueprint). (Oversize-folder C1D2F8)
    - Interior Elevations, Cupola Detail, and Feed Bin Detail, 10 of 11. Russel Associates. 1990 May. Pellet Print (Positive blueprint). (Oversize-folder C1D2F8)
    - Door Schedule, Room Schedule, 11 of 11. Russel Associates. 1990 May. Pellet Print (Positive blueprint). (Oversize-folder C1D2F8)
    - Drawing Showing Purposed Changes in Tower of Garage Building at "Duke Farms". J.C. Deagan, Inc. 1939 Sep 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D8F9b)
    - Foundation Plan, Stable for J.B. Duke. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1900 Jun 16. Blueprint. (Tube TU202)
    - First Floor Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1900 Aug 24. Blueprint. (Tube TU202)
    - Second Floor Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1900 Aug 24. Blueprint. (Tube TU202)
    - Second Floor Plan [revisions]. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [1900]. Blueprint. (Tube TU202)
    - Full-Size Details of Desk in Office in stable for J.B. Duke Esq. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1901 Feb 12. Pencil and watercolor. (Tube TU203)
    - Full Size Details of Office Partition in stable for J.B. Duke Esq. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1901 Feb 11. Pencil and watercolor. (Tube TU203)
    - F.S. Detail of China Closet & Pantry in stable for J.B. Duke Esq. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1900 Aug 2. Pencil and watercolor. (Tube TU203)
    - F.S. Details of Copper Finials, Hip and Ridge Rolls, Stable for J.B. Duke. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1900 May 31. Pencil and watercolor. (Tube TU204)
    - F.S. Detail of Copper Finial for Bell Tower, Stable for J.B. Duke. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1900 May 31. Pencil and watercolor. (Tube TU204)
    - F.S. Detail of Weather Vane, Stable for J.B. Duke Esq. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. 1900 Sep 8. Pencil and watercolor, photocopy. (Tube TU204)
  - Duke Farms Main Residence, 1907, 1932-1941, 1966, 1985 and undated
    - Reflector Detail to Illuminate Glass Shades in Vestibule Between Hall & Bedroom No. 1. Frink Corp., Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 May 19. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F1)
    - Scale & F.S. Detail of Concealed Door & Frame in Entrance Hall. Lagana & Co., Inc. [Circa 1936]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F1)
    - Scale & F.S. D. of Ent. Hall, Alterations to Panelling, Etc. Lagana & Co., Inc. 1936 Dec 23. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F1)
    - [New Water Line and Water Softener Installation]. Undated. Pencil and marker, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C1D1F1)
    - Entrance. [Circa 1932]. Pencil. (Oversize-folder C1D1F1)
    - Office of Mr. Cooley. [Circa 1960s]. Color pencil. (Oversize-folder C1D1F1)
    - Details of New Book Shelves in Living Hall, Drwg No. 1010. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 May 27. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F1)
    - Plumbing-Bar, Powder Room, Mr. Cooley Residence. Undated. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C1D1F1)
    - Cut Stone Work, Additions to Residence of James B. Duke. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Aug 6. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - 1/2" Scale Drawing of Caps and Splays to Chimneys. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Sep 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - Full Size Details of Bay Window in Palm Room. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Sep 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - 1/2" Scale Detail of New End Gable. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Sep 13. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - 1/2" Scale Detail of Double Gable. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Oct 22. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - 1/2" Scale Detail of Kitchen Gable. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Sep 13. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - 1/2" Scale Detail of Kitchen Gable. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Oct 23. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - Stairs from Servants' Dining Room. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Oct 3. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - 1/2" Scale Detail of Central Portion and So. Front. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Sep 6. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - 1/2" Scale Detail of Central Portion of So. Front. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Oct 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - Drawing Showing Boiler Flue Changed to Hall Chimney. Henry H. Kendall, architect. 1907 Oct 30. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - Detail of Hood at Servants Entrance. Henry H. Kendall, architect. [1907]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F2)
    - Plan of Third Floor Over Bedroom #1, Scheme D. Matthews Construction Co., Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Feb 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F3)
    - Book Room - Scheme B. Matthews Construction Co., Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Feb 10, revised 1936 Mar 6. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F3)
    - Alternate Scheme for Bedroom Showing Various Window Arrangements, Scheme D. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Feb 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F3)
    - F.S.D. Music Room Vestibule. [McMillen, Inc.]. [1936]. Pencil on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Music Room. [McMillen, Inc.]. [1936]. Pencil on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - North Wall-Music Room. [McMillen, Inc.]. [1936]. Pencil on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - F.S.D. Cornice and Pillaster Cap, Music Room. [McMillen, Inc.]. [1936]. Pencil on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Music Room Vestibule. McMillen, Inc. 1937 Jan 14. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Second Floor Hall, Linen Cabinet, Full Scale Details. McMillen, Inc. 1937 Feb 2. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Second Floor Hall, Linen Cabinet, Elevation. McMillen, Inc. 1937 Feb 2. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Entrence [sic] Hall. McMillen, Inc. 1940 May 27. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - [Palm Room Alteration - Fountain]. McMillen, Inc. 1940 May 28. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - [Palm Room Alterations]. McMillen, Inc. 1940 Jun 4. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Reception. McMillen, Inc. 1940 Jun 5. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Gallery. McMillen, Inc. 1940 Jun 5. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Dining Room. McMillen, Inc. [1936]. Pencil on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - Dining Room, Straight Pillaster. McMillen, Inc. [1936]. Pencil on tracing paper. (Oversize-folder C1D1F4)
    - [Window Details], Sheet 1. Brown, Archibald Manning, Hope's Windows Inc. 1937 Jan 12. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F5)
    - [Casement Windows & Doors], Sheet 2. Brown, Archibald Manning, Hope's Windows Inc. 1937 Jan 12. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F5)
    - Frmg. 2nd Fl Residence. Savary & Glaser, Inc. 1937 Jan 3. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F5)
    - [Double Door, Details & Sections]. Savary & Glaser, Inc. 1937 Dec 30. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F5)
    - Living Room, F.S. Profile Section thru Bookcase, F.S. Profile Section thru Door and Door Reveal. McMillen, Inc., interior architect. 1936 Nov 15. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F6)
    - Living Room, Passage to Music Room. McMillen, Inc., interior architect. 1936 Nov 15. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F6)
    - Living Room. McMillen, Inc., interior architect. 1936 Nov 15. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F6)
    - Music Room. McMillen, Inc., interior architect. 1936 Oct 20. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F6)
    - Dining Room. McMillen, Inc., interior architect. 1936 Oct 19. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F6)
    - Dining Room, Full Pillaster, Detail of Base Exactly Like Old Base. McMillen, Inc., interior architect. 1936 Dec 10. Vellum. (Oversize-folder C1D1F6)
    - James Cromwell Esq. Own Bedroom - Suggested Scheme for Decoration, Sheet 2. L. Alavoine & Co. [Circa 1936]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F7)
    - Shade Brackets for U.S. Dept. of Agriculture, Washington, D.C. W.H. Lutton & Co. 1936 May 11. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F7)
    - Shade Tracks, Sheet No. 6. D.C. W.H. Lutton & Co. 1938 Aug 12. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F7)
    - Detail of Two Windows for Bed Rm #2 Showing Radiator Enclosures. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 May 24. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F7)
    - Details of Glass Doors in Vestibule Between Hall & Bedroom. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Aug 5. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F7)
    - Plan, Smoking Room. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Sep 30. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F7)
    - Elevations. Wyeth & King, architects. [1936 Sep 30]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F7)
    - Details of Powder Room. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Dec 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F7)
    - Elevation at Gable End. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 May 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F8)
    - F.S. Detail of Existing Cornice Showing Reduced Projection & New Gutter. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Jun 9. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F8)
    - Detail of Dormers for East End of South Elevation. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Jun 28. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F8)
    - Detail of Dormer Cornice. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Jul 26. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F8)
    - Layout of Terrace - East End of South Elevation. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Aug 5. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F8)
    - F.S.D. of Casement Doors, F.S.D. of Casement Windows on South Elev. (East End). Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Aug 27. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F8)
    - [Exterior Elevations East Wing]. Wyeth & King, architects. [Circa 1937]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F8)
    - West End of South Elevation, Half-Elevation of End Gable. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 May 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F9)
    - [Third Floor Alterations]. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 May 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F9)
    - Second Floor Plan, Third Floor Plan. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Jun 7. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F9)
    - Elevation - Section. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Jun 7. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F9)
    - North View of Main Entrance. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Jul 27. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D1F9)
    - Alterations to Bedroom and Baths Second Floor -Scheme B. Matthews Construction Co.; Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Feb 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D2F6)
    - Patterns for Rubber Tile Floors. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Apr 27. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D2F6)
    - Bath Room Elevations, Second Floor. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Jul 20. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D2F6)
    - Entrance Hall #1, Scheme A. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Sep 15. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C1D2F7)
    - Proposed Additions to Residence of James B. Duke, Esq. Basement Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [circa 1908]. Pencil and pen on board, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F3)
    - Proposed Additions to Residence of James B. Duke, Esq. First Floor Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [circa 1908]. Pencil and pen on board, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F3)
    - Proposed Additions to Residence of James B. Duke, Esq. Second Floor Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [circa 1908]. Pencil and pen on board, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F3)
    - Proposed Additions to Residence of James B. Duke, Esq. Attic Floor Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [circa 1908]. Pencil and pen on board, photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F3)
    - Basement Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [circa 1908]. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F7)
    - First Floor Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [circa 1908]. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F7)
    - Second Floor Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [circa 1908]. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F7)
    - Attic Floor Plan. Kendall, Taylor & Stevens, architects. [circa 1908]. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C2D7F7)
    - Revised Terrace Plan Off New Addition to House. Innocenti & Webel. [circa 1939]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F1)
    - Details for Terrace Off New Room. Innocenti & Webel. [circa 1939]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F1)
    - Auditorium Building. Savary & Glaeser, Inc. 1938 Aug 9. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F1)
    - General Planting Plan for the Tennis Court Building on the Estate of Mrs. James B. Duke. Ellen Shipman. 1933 Apr. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F1)
    - Basement, Light Hazard [Plan of Fire Suppression System], 1 of 2. Viking Fire Protection Company; Lorenz, J. 1966 Feb 10. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F1)
    - Basement, Light Hazard [Plan of Fire Suppression System], 2 of 2. Viking Fire Protection Company; Lorenz, J. 1966 Feb 17. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F1)
    - Suggested Treatment for the Winter Bird Quarters. Innocenti & Webel. 1939 Jan. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F1)
    - Main Line. S.R.C. undated. Photocopy. (Oversize-folder C3D1F1)
    - Playhouse, Duke Farms. Croft Steel Windows Inc.; Lamb, Thomas W. 1938 Aug 15. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Modern Room - Stage. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jun 29. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Modern Room. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jun 29. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Modern Room. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jun 29. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Study for Flat Roof Scheme. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jun 29. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Plan of Foundation. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jul 11. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Plan of First Floor. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jul 11. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Revised Front Elevation. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jul 12. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Revised Side Elevation. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jul 12. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Reinforcing of Concrete Walls. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Aug 4. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Detail of Base and Roque Curbing. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Sep 29. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F2)
    - Ceiling Light Cove. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Sep 30. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F3)
    - Auditorium Elevations. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Sep 30. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F3)
    - Plan of Basement. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jul 29. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F3)
    - Plan of First Floor. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Jul 29. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F3)
    - Miscellaneous Details in Auditorium. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Oct 17. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F3)
    - Layout of Roque Cushion. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Oct 25. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F3)
    - Revised Details of Curtain Slot & Base. Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1939 Jan 13. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F3)
    - Tennis Court Building for Mrs. J.B. Duke, Lobby & Stair Hall, Interior Plans & Elevations, Drawing 102. James W. O'Connor, architect. 1932 Apr 18. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F4)
    - Tennis Court Building for Mrs. J.B. Duke, Bar & Tap Rooms, Interior Elevations & Plan, Drawing 103. James W. O'Connor, architect. 1932 Apr 18. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F4)
    - Tennis Court Building for Mrs. J.B. Duke, Lounge- Interior Elevations, Drawing 104. James W. O'Connor, architect. 1932 Apr 18. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F4)
    - Tennis Court Building for Mrs. J.B. Duke, Gallery (on Lounge Level) - Interior Elevations, Drawing 105. James W. O'Connor, architect. 1932 Apr 18. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F4)
    - Tennis Court Building for Mrs. J.B. Duke, Swimming Pool Room - Interior Elevation, Drawing 106. James W. O'Connor, architect. 1932 Apr 18. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F4)
    - Alterations to Residence of Mrs. James B. Duke, Basement & Foundation Plan, Drawing 1. James W. O'Connor, architect. [circa 1932]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F5)
    - Alterations to Residence of Mrs. James B. Duke, First Floor Plan, Drawing 2. James W. O'Connor, architect. [circa 1932]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F5)
    - Alterations to Residence of Mrs. James B. Duke, Second Floor Plan, Drawing 3. James W. O'Connor, architect. [circa 1932]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F5)
    - Alterations to Residence of Mrs. James B. Duke, North-West Elevation, Drawing 4. James W. O'Connor, architect. [circa 1932]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F5)
    - Alterations to Residence of Mrs. James B. Duke, South-West Elevation, Drawing 5. James W. O'Connor, architect. [circa 1932]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F5)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Plan of Main Hall Showing Proposed Alterations. Frank Partridge Inc. [circa 1930s]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Details of Fountain Support, Dwg No R-1. John W. Ryan Co. 1940 Oct 28. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Detail of Slab Under Fountain, Dwg No R-2. John W. Ryan Co. 1940 Oct 28. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Passage to Library, Dwg No R-3. John W. Ryan Co. 1940 Oct 18. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, F.S. Details Head, Jamb, Sill for Steel Sash at South Elevation- Palm Room, Dwg No R-4. John W. Ryan Co. 1940 Oct 25. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, F.S. Detail Door Jamb, Head & Sill at East Elev. of Palm Rm. West Elevation Similar, Dwg No R-5. John W. Ryan Co. 1940 Oct 25. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Fountain Support, Dwg. 51. John W. Ryan Co. 1940 Oct 28. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Wall at Tennis Building. Innocenti & Webel. 1938 Sep 20. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, East Elevation of Porte-Cochere, Dwg No. 503. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Aug 16. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Ent. Hall, Passage & Gallery. McMillen Inc. 1940 Jun 6. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Detail Sheet of Air Conditioning System. Kimball, Dwight D.; Lamb, Thomas W.; Woolfolk, Edward G. 1938 Oct 30; revised 1938 Nov 12. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Alterations to Mrs. James B. Duke Residence, Main Buildings. John C. Paige & Co. Inc. Insurance. 1932 Jan. Diazo. (Oversize-folder C3D1F6)
    - Wall and Steps at the Box Garden. Innocenti & Webel. 1938 Aug 22. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7b)
    - Flag Diagram for Terrace off Garden. Innocenti & Webel. [1938] Sep. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7b)
    - Guide Planting Plan for the Garden Area. Innocenti & Webel. [1938] Sep 3. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7b)
    - Playhouse Plan and Elevations (Diagramatic). Thomas W. Lamb, architect. 1938 Sep 27. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7b)
    - [Palm Room]. McMillen Inc./ S.F. 1940 May 27. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D1F7b)
    - Plot Plan, Tennis Court Building. James O'Connor, architect. 1932 Apr 18. Blueprint, transparency. (Oversize-folder C3D1F9)
    - Rubber Tile Layout [Partial]. Swern & Company. 1936 May 8. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F1)
    - Hall & Passage I Floor, II Floor Lighting Plan. Rudolf Wendel, Inc. 1940 Oct 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F1)
    - Plan & Elevations of Walls of Solarium. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F1)
    - Alterations to Residence of Mrs. James Cromwell, Details of Third Floor Wardrobe. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 May 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F1)
    - Details of Glass and Metal Doors for Recessed Cabinets, First Floor in Residence. Kromm and Kohl; McMillen Inc. [1936]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F1)
    - Elevations of Main Hall, Showing Suggested Alterations, Dwg No. 2. Frank Partridge Inc., Leonard L. Lock. [circa 1930s]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F2)
    - Details for Grading & Walks Adjorning Tennis Building. Innocenti & Webel. [1938] Sep 21. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F2)
    - Glass and Metal Mantel for Bed Room No. 1. Kromm and Kohl; Wyeth & King. 1936 Mar 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F2)
    - Revisions to Book Room, 2 pairs doors to cover book shelves right side of mantel, shelf added to mantel. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 May 19. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F2)
    - Details of Wardrobes. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 May 19. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F2)
    - Proposed Alteration to Residence of Mrs. J.H.R. Cromwell, [Plan and Exterior Elevations East Wing]. Wyeth & King, architects. [circa 1937]. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F2)
    - 1-1/2" Casement Section Sash & Doors. J.S. Thorn Company; John W. Ryan Co. 1940 Nov 13. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Custom Built Casement Windows & Doors. J.S. Thorn Company; John W. Ryan Co. 1940 Nov 13. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Dressing Room, Rubber Tile Fl., Wood Base. Wyeth & King; Paul Coste Inc. 1936 May 4. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Alterations to Mr. Inman's Bathroom. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Aug 18. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Details of Bed Room #1, Detail of Bath No.1. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Details of Bath Room No.2 (Mr. Cromwell). Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Details of Windows #1-#2 and #3 and Radiator Enclosure. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 13. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Details of Windows for Bed Rm #1 & Dressing Rm. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 17. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Dressing Room. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 24. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Details of Radiator for Window #10, Bath Rm #1. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 24. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4a)
    - Full Size Details of Bath Rm No.1. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 24. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4b)
    - Details of New Work at Hall & Music Room Where Porch is Removed. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Apr 9. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4b)
    - F.S.D. Showing Changes in Casement Frame for Bath Rm. Behind Chimney 3rd Fl.. Wyeth & King, architects. 1937 Jun 10. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4b)
    - Detail of "Wheatley" Chimney Pots. Wyeth & King; Cambridge Wheatley Co. 1937 Jun 11. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4b)
    - Bronze Hinged Sash. General Bronze Corporation; John W. Ryan Co. 1941 Jan 6. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4b)
    - Specification, Description of Work Contemplated. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Feb 18. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4b)
    - F.S. Detail Radiator Enclosure. Wyeth & King, architects. 1936 Mar 24. Blueprint. (Oversize-folder C3D2F4b)